[{"answer": "Not if they don't catch us, my friend", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Because if you don't take the chance, you're already dead", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Three white males shot Junior.  my friend followed them to York Estates", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "York Estates.  Fou", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Chief?  my friend said a young girl answered the door", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " He didn't say", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "But if you stay in this house, I can promise you this", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You can't imagine the fucking you're going to get", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "that place shows six lines into the house. They blocked all six like you wanted", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes, sir.  They'll only accept calls from your cell", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You gotta pee", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Either I'm going to tie you or Mars will tie you.  Which do you want", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I want a helicopter to take us to that place", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'll give you these people", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "They have security cameras.  my friend would see you coming", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No.  He said that his father's unconsciou", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That you, my friend", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You oughta try on the problem I got in here", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What do you want me to do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What do you want me to do", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "He has lots of disks", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I thought they locked you in your room", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Can you get into the office", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I can get into the crawlspace from my closet and climb all over the house", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I can get into the den.  The office is right across the hall", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "We're fucked", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "There is no way out", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Two hundred thousand cash, right in your pocket, no one needs to know", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "There's a million dollars in there, maybe two million.  I'll give you half", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What happened", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I can't go without my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Do you want to go or not?  I'm offering you a way out of here", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "All three of us will go, but we have to move fast.  Mars and my friend don't know I'm doing this", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Not until the man calls", "docId": "Hostage.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "They've been in there all day", "qsentId": 36}]